Guide to the Printed Ephemera Related to African American Political Activism and Arts
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Printed ephemera of African American political activism and arts
1913-1990
1963-1976
JWJ MSS 36
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
2.3
(3 boxes) + 3 broadside folders
Printed ephemera related to African American political activism and arts primarily in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, circa 1913-1990, with the bulk of the material from 1963 to 1976. Significant organizations documented in the collection include the Philadelphia chapters of the Black Panther Party and Peace and Freedom Party, as well as local and national electoral campaigns of the Communist Party of the United States of America. Many of the items document speakers and events sponsored by political, art, and social pressure groups. Items include handbills, leaflets, direct mail, posters, and other printed ephemera.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from William Reese Company on the James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection of Negro Arts & Letters Fund, 2007.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Printed ephemera related to African American political activism and arts primarily in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, circa 1913-1990, with the bulk of the material from 1963 to 1976. Significant organizations documented in the collection include the Philadelphia chapters of the Black Panther Party and Peace and Freedom Party, as well as local and national electoral campaigns of the Communist Party of the United States of America. Many of the items document speakers and events sponsored by political, art, and social pressure groups. Items include handbills, leaflets, direct mail, posters, and other printed ephemera
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into three series according to size to faciliate its storage and handling.
African American political activists -- Ephemera; African American politicians -- Ephemera; African Americans -- Ephemera; African Americans -- Civil rights -- Ephemera; African Americans -- Pennsylvania -- Philadelphia -- Ephemera; Black power -- Ephemera; Civil Rights movements -- United States -- Ephemera; Political activists -- United States -- Ephemera; Pressure groups -- United States -- Ephemera; Philadelphia (Pa.) -- Race relations; Direct mail; Handbills; Leaflets; Posters; Printed ephemera; Black Panther Party -- Ephemera; Communist Party of the United States of America -- Ephemera; Peace and Freedom Party (U.S.) -- Ephemera
- Ephemera, circa 1913-1990; Series I; (2 boxes)
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically by by the corporate name, and in a few instances the personal surname, of the creator or title of a serial, and chronologically therein, followed by ephemera with unidentified creators arranged chronologically.
  - Aframerican News Service (Atlanta, Georgia)
    - Leaflet. Stokely Carmichael Speaks to Black People of South Carolina, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - African Cultural and Historical Society (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Handbill. Gala Garvey Day Celebration, 1968 Aug 17; (4 items) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Afro-Am Alliance (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Photocopy. Afro-Am Speaks, no date (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Afro-Am Publishing Company (Chicago, Illinois)
    - Direct mail. Join in the observation of Negro History Week, Feb. 7-13, 1965 Feb; (5 items) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Albert Saifer, Publisher (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Advertisements. W. E. B. DuBois, Black Reconstruction, 1966; (3 items) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alexander Defense Committee (New York, New York)
    - Leaflet. This is South Africa, circa 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Council of Christian Churches (New York, New York)
    - Leaflet. There is a Difference Between Black and White, no date (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith (New York, New York)
    - Leaflet. Resource Units on Intergroup Relations: Desegregation in Public Schools, circa 1954 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Leaflet. Annotated bibliographies on Human Relations, circa 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Leaflet. Resource Units on Intergroup Relations: Prejudice and Discrimination, circa 1955 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Press Release. Paul Hartman, "New Threat to Human Rights Agencies", 1957 May 3 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Leaflet. Resource Units on Intergroup Relations: Desegregation in Public Schools, circa 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Associated Publishers, Inc. (Washington, District of Columbia)
    - Leaflet. Negro Makers of History, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Leaflet. Distinguished Personalities, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Handbill. Large Pictures, no date (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Association for the Study of Negro Life and History (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Card. Invitation to 50th Anniversary Awards Luncheon, 1966 Feb 12 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Association for the Study of Negro Life and History (Washington, District of Columbia)
    - Handbill. Negro History Week, 1965 Feb 7-14; (2 items) (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Calendars., 1965; (2 items) (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Program. Association for the Study of Negro Life and History, no date (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bel-Ad Records (Los Angeles, California)
    - Leaflet. Dahle Scott, vocalist and actress, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Black Community Fund (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Handbill. Blackmas, 1969 Dec 19-21 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Black House (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Handbill. Open House, 1967 Oct 8 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Handbill. Schedule, 1967 Nov (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Black Panther Party (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Handbill. People's Enemy No. 1, circa 1967; (2 items) (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Handbill. Community Meetings, circa 1967-1971 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Handbill. Free Health Clinic, circa 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Handbill. Cisco-Kidd Pig, Rizzo Oinks Again!, circa 1970; (2 items) (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Handbill. Revolutionary Intercommunal Solidarity Day Rally, 1971 Mar 6-7; (2 items) (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Boston Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression (Boston, Massachusetts)
    - Leaflet. Boston Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression, circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Broadside Press (Detroit, Michigan)
    - Advertisement. Poems of Negro Revolt, circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Bronze Art Card Guild (Richmond, Virginia)
    - Greeting Cards. Douglas (sic) and Lincoln Confer, no date (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Chicago Defender Newspaper (Chcago, Illinois)
    - Envelope, no date (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Citizens for Jim Barber (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Circulars. James Barber, Pennsylvania House of Representatives, circa 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Civil Rights Congress (New York, New York)
    - Leaflet. The Charge is Jim Crow, circa 1954 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Leaflet. Your Liberty is Imprisoned with William L. Patterson, circa 1954 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Club Five (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Ticket. Celebrate Negro History Week, 1963 Feb 23 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Comay Productions (New York, New York)
    - Handbill. Lorenz Graham Jr., no date (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Committee for the Freedom of William Worth (New York, New York)
    - Leaflet., circa 1963 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Committee to Defend Fletcher Mills (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Direct mail. Letter for assistance, 1952 Jun 13 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Handbill. Help Fletcher Mills, circa 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Committee to Free Angela Davis (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Handbill. Family Affair Dance, 1971 Dec 17; (3 items) (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Committee to Free Martin Sostre (New York, New York)
    - Leaflet. "Not for his Crimes, but for His Ideas", 1975 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Communist Party USA
    - Photocopy. Resolution on Aid to Texas, 1950 Jan 27-28 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Fliers. Invitation to meet Michael Zagarell in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1968; (2 items) (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Leaflet. Jarvis Tyner, Communist Candidate for Vice-President, 1976; (5 items) (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Pamphlet. Henry Winston, Solidarity Strategy for Victory Against Apartheid, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Leaflet. Memorial tribute to Henry Winston, 1987 Jan 11 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Congress of Racial Equality (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Handbill. All Africa Day, 1969 May 25 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Congress of Racial Equality (Washington, District of Columbia)
    - Program. Club Aquilas "Purlie Victorious", 1963 Aug 28-29 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Program. Testimonial for Julius W. Hobson, 1964 May 2 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Council on African Affairs (New York, New York)
    - Petition. South Africa, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - DuBois Memorial Committee (New York, New York)
    - Pamphlet. A Souvenir Program in Memory of Dr. William E. Burghardt DuBois, 1868-1963, 1963 Feb 23; (2 items) (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Edward E. Strong Memorial Educational Fund (Brooklyn and Richmond Hill, New York)
    - Leaflet. Announcing the Memorial Educational Trust fund, circa 1957 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Emergency Conference Committee (Chicago, Illinois)
    - Leaflet. An Emergency Call, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Fair Play for Cuba Committee (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Handbill. William Worthy Event, 1961, Dec (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Fasson (Painesville, Ohio)
    - Stickers. Johnson for Integration, Goldwater for President, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation (Nyack, New York)
    - Envelope. The Montgomery Story, no date (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Free Library of Philadelphia (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Leaflet. That All Men May be Free, 1963 Feb (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Freedom Action Committee (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Leaflet. FAC, circa 1975; (4 items) (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Statement, circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Freedom Greeting Card Company (Bensalem, Pennsylvania)
    - Handbill. Freedom Greeting Cards Sold at this Store, circa 1969 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Freedomways Associates (New York, New York)
    - Leaflet. Advertisement for "Ballad for Bimshire" in New York, New York, 1963 Oct (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Harmon Foundation (New York, New York)
    - Leaflet. Alexander "Skunder" Boghossian, Ethiopian Painter, 1965 Nov-Dec (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - International Peace Mission Movement (Kingston, New York)
    - Handbill. Mass Meeting, 1941 Oct 12 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Jewish Affairs (New York, New York)
    - Leaflet. Lloyd L. Brown, Telling the Truth About Paul Robeson, 1981; (2 items) (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Kennedy, Florynce R., Attorney
    - Leaflet. Life for Death Benefit, 1974 Aug 20; (3 items) (Box 1, Folder 66)
      General note
      Manscript on verso of an item discusses the drug use of Billie Holiday, the singer
  - Kraft Publishing Company (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Leaflet. Advertisement for "Before We Became Strangers," which probably became "Give Me a Child," by Sarah E. Wright and Lucy Smith, circa 1955; (3 items) (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Labor Committee for Peace in Vietnam (New York, New York)
    - Direct mail. Chain letter distribution of a pamphlet, 1966 Jun (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Lee Cultural Center (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Handbill. The Anatomy of the Black Aesthetic, 1969 Apr; (2 items) (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Handbill. Talk by John O Killens, 1969 Nov 21; (4 items) (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Handbill. Black Spectrum Theatre, 1975; (3 items) (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Liberation Committee for Africa (New York, New York)
    - Handbill. Negro History Week Observance, 1963 Feb 10; (2 items) (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Lincoln Dames (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Envelope and stationery, no date (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Louis E. Burnham Fund (New York, New York)
    - Leaflet. Louis E. Burnham (September 29, 1915-Fenruary 12, 1960) (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - McGovern for President (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Handbill. Nixon Doesn't Want Us to Vote, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Mercy-Douglass Hospital Campaign (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Letterhead., circa 1950-1962 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Certificate of Leadership, circa 1950-1962 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Michael Hughes Production
    - Leaflet. W. E. B. Dubois on Intelligence, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Monteiro for Congress Committee (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Handbill. Calendar of Events and 30,000 Jobs, 1972 Jun (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Direct mail. Campaign Worker Kick-Off Rally, 1972 Jul 31 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Leaflet. 30,000 New Jobs, circa 1972; (2 items) (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Leaflet. Anthony Monteiro... A People's Candidate with A People's Program, circa 1972; (4 items) (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - National Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression (New York, New York)
    - Leaflet. 2nd Annual Conference, 1974 May 9-12 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Roll. Members, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (New York, New York)
    - Direct Mail. Address by Ralph Bunche, 1951 Mar 23 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Leaflet. Stop This Murder!, 1951 Aug (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Reprint. Joe Alex Morris, "The Truth About the Florida Race Troubles", 1952 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Leaflet. "We never claimed it to be authentic", 1956 Oct; (2 items) (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (Northeastern Region)
    - Ticket. Raffle for a United States Savings Bond at Bleecker Stadium in Albany, New York, 1950 Jul 3 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Business cards. Harry A. Vodery, circa 1965 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (Pasadena, California)
    - Advertisement, no date; (2 items) (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - National Baptist Foreign Missions Retreat for Foreign Missionaries (Washington, District of Columbia)
    - Leaflet. National Baptist Foreign Missions Retreat for Foreign Missionaries, 1961; (2 items) (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - National Day for Black Unity Against the War in Vietnam (New York, New York)
    - Leaflet., 1968 May 19-20 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - National Negro Labor Council (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Leaflet. Greetings to Initial Affair, no date (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - National United Committee to Free Angela Davis (San Francisco, California)
    - Direct mail. Advertisement for If They Came in the Morning, by Angela Davis, circa 1971 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - New World Resource Center (Chicago, Illinois)
    - Handbill. Talk by Irwin Silber, circa 1972-1978 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - New York Committee to Free Angela Davis (New York, New York)
    - Pamphlet. A Political Biography of Angela Davis, circa 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Newsweek, Cover story, "Black Mood on Campus", 1969 Feb 10 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Non-Partisan Committee for the Election of Negroes (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Handbill. Vote Negroes into Office, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Opportunities Industrialization Centers (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Handbill. First Annual Philadelphia Black Unity Football Classic, 1970 Sep 26 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Othello Recording Corporation (New York, New York)
    - Leaflet. Paul Robeson, Solid Rock: Favorite Hymns of My People, circa 1953 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Peace and Freedom Party (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Leaflet. Dick Gregory for President, 1968 Sep 24 (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Leaflet. Dick Gregory for President, 1968; (2 items) (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Leaflet. Dick Gregory for President, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - Document. Decision-Making in the Peace and Freedom Party, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - Handbill. Dick Gregory for President, 1968; (4 items) (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Philadelphia City Council
    - Resolution. Desegredation of Girard College, 1954 May (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Philadelphia Militant Forum (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Ticket. 1965: Prospects for Freedom, 1965 Apr 2 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Philadelphia Social Science Forum (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Handbill. Africa, National Liberation & Peace, 1959 Dec (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Handbill. Benjamin J. Davis, 1963; (2 items) (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Handbill. Two Views: Claude Lightfoot and Wright Palmer, 1968 Feb; (3 items) (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - Handbill. James E. Jackson, 1977 Oct 21 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Plainfield Joint Defense Committee (Plainfield, New Jersey)
    - Leaflet. Speak Out! For the Release of Plainfield's Black Hostages, 1970; (2 items) (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Playbill, "To be Young, Gifted, and Black", 1969 Jul (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Progressive Women of Philadelphia (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Leaflet. Cavalcade of Negro Art, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Real People's Party (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Leaflet. William R. Davis for State Senate, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Shaw-Barton Calendar Company, George Beach Studios (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), and the American Negro Commemorative Society
    - Calendar. The Great American Negro Calendar, 1971, 1975; (3 items) (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Shaw-Barton Calendar Company and George Beach Studios (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Calendar. The Afro-American Historical Calendar, 1979, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 118-119)
  - Sons of Africa Club (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Handbill. Authentic Dance & Cultural Show, 1969 Oct 24; (2 items) (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Student Mobilization Committee, Third World Task Force (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Handbill. National Peace Action Day, 1970 Oct 31 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Temple University (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Invitation. Reception in honor of Charles L. Blockson, 1983 Nov 3 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Thomas Nabried Center for Marxist-Leninist Education (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Handbill. Annette Conn, 1974 Mar (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Handbill. How to Fight for Your Welfare Rights, 1974 Jul (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Leaflets for programs, 1974-1976; (16 items) (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Union Women United for Humphrey-Muskie (Washington, District of Columbia)
    - Leaflet. Women Say..., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Unity Mission Church, Home and Training School, Inc. (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Invitation. Banquet and Dedication Services by Father Divine, 1947, Feb 15-16 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Universal Negro Improvement Association and African Communities League (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Letterhead, circa 1940-1950 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Veterans Unity for Peace & Freedom (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Handbill. Veterans Unity for Peace & Freedom, 1970 Mar 13 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Washington School of Welding (Washington Court House, Ohio)
    - Handbill. Attention Ex-G.I.'s (White and Colored) Learn a Trade, circa 1950 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - WDAS, Radio 1480 (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Halftone. Joe Rainey, circa 1965 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Women Strike for Peace (Washington, District of Columbia)
    - Handbill. Hear Conrad Lynn, 1968 Mar 15 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - World Emancipation Exposition of Philadelphia (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Cards. Invitation to the exposition, 1964 Sep 30-Oct 4 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Youth for Monteiro Committee (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Handbill. Monteiro for Congress, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Gamma Kappa Zeta Chapter (Texarkana, Texas)
    - Leaflet. Miss Blue Revue, 1976 Dec 3; (2 items) (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Unidentified Creators
    - Handbill. John Brown, The Liberator, circa 1913 (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Handbill. Sam J. Ntiro, circa 1964 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Handbill. Vote for A. Benjamin Johnson, Jr., 1969 May 20 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - Handbill. Rizzo Must Go!, 1970; (2 items) (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - Handbill. Black People Boycott, 1970; (3 items) (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - Photocopy. Juan Mari Brás, "The Decisive Way", circa 1972 (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - Stickers: Impeach Nixon, circa 1974 (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - Circular. Negro National Anthem, no date (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - Leaflet. Hymns, no date (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - Sticker. Black American Heritage Flag, no date (Box 2, Folder 145)
- Ephemera, Oversize, 1950- circa 1986; Series II; (1 box) + 3 broadside folders
  Arranged alphabetically by the corporate name of the creator, and chronologically therein, followed by very large oversize ephemera in broadside folders.
  - African-Americans for Friendship and Retainment of Our Image, Culture and Arts (New York, New York)
    - Poster. 6th Annual African Ambassadors' Ball and Dinner, 1970 Nov 1 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Black Fire Production (Washington, District of Columbia)
    - Poster. Unity in Double Affair, Baltimore & D.C. Concert, 1975 Aug 8-9; (2 items) (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - Christian Science Monitor newspaper
    - Reprint. [Dick] Gregory says 'honesty' key to U.S. race problem, 1968 Jan 27; (2 items) (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Civil Rights Congress (New York, New York)
    - Direct Mail. The Story of Willie McGee, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - Communist Party USA (New York, New York)
    - Poster. Henry Winston. "They Robbed me of my Sight but not my Vision", circa 1966-1986; (2 items) (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Congress of Racial Equality (New York, New York)
    - Leaflet. Passive Resisance to Massive Resistance, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Hall-Tyner Election Campaign Committee (New York, New York)
    - Poster. Angela Davis Urges - Declare your Independence, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - Lee Cultural Center (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Poster. The Anatomy of the Black Aesthetic, 1969 Apr (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Lee Cultural Center (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), American Exhibiting Artists (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), and Philadelphia Department of Recreation
    - Poster. Philadelphia Negro Artist, 1967 Feb 10-Mar 3 (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - Left Bank Jazz Society of Washington, D.C. (Washington, District of Columbia)
    - Poster. Spring Concert Series, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - National Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression (New York, New York)
    - Poster. Stop Racism and Repression, 1974 Jul 4; (3 items) (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - November 4th Committee (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Poster. Election '72. Hear Angela Davis, 1972; (2 items) (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - Organization of Solidarity with the People of Asia, Africa and Latin America (Havana, Cuba)
    - Poster. Day of Solidarity with the People of Laos, October 12, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - Poster. Solidarity with Syria, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Poster. Together with Viet Nam, 1971; (2 items) (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Poster. Day of Solidarity with Puerto Rico, 1974, Sep 23 (Box 3, Folder 161)
  - Philadelphia Social Science Forum (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania) and National Anti-Imperialist Movement in Solidarity with African Liberations (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Poster. Film, Ethiopia: The Burden of the Past and Road to the Future, 1979 Jan 19; (4 items) (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - Wall Street Journal newspaper
    - Reprint. "Comic With a Cause", 1967 Dec 4 (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - Young Workers Liberation League (New York, New York)
    - Poster. Here We Stand for Peace, Jobs, Equality; Here We Stand to Live Like Paul Robeson, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 164)
- Ephemera in Broadside Folders, 1981-1985; (3 broadside folders)
  - April Actions for Peace, Jobs, & Justice (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Poster. Protest Days in Washington, D.C., 1985 Apr 20 (Box Bsd, folder 165)
  - Communist Party USA (New York, New York)
    - Poster. Rally with Gus Hall and Angela Davis, 1984 Aug 26 (Box Bsd, folder 166)
  - Conference in Solidarity with the Liberation Struggles of the Peoples of Southern Africa (New York, New York)
    - Poster. Protest Rally, Stop U.S. Support for South African Racists, 1981 Oct 10 (Box Bsd, folder 167)